UNITE Communications Department Audio-Visual Materials 6000/037 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Organizing Committee - Tues. June 29 - UNITE Convention 1999, 33 (Box 10)
- TogetherWe'll do better UNITE! - Aug. 3, 1997, 34 (Box 10)
- Together We'll do better UNITE! -- Aug. 3, 1997, 35 (Box 10)
- Hillary Clinton Sews Union Label - 3/6/1996, 36 (Box 10)
- Hillary Clinton Sews Union Label - 3/6/1996, 37 (Box 10)
- TogetherWe'll do better UNITE!, 38 (Box 10)
- GRI Video 1 - March 1995, 39 (Box 10)
- GRI Video 1 - March 1995, 40 (Box 10)
- GRI Video 1 - March 1995, 41 (Box 10)
- Make it happen, 42 (Box 10)
- El Tiempo es ya Kastrin, 43 (Box 10)
- Depende de Usted!, 44 (Box 10)
- Ain't no stopping us now - Morse Automotive, 45 (Box 10)
- Ain't no stopping us, 46 (Box 10)
- Ain't no stopping us now - Morse Automotive, 47 (Box 10)